(Leonard:)- Hey.
- What?
(Howard:)Nothing.
(Sheldon:)Smart, we don't want any problems.
(Amy:)I can't believe I ditched work
for Disneyland.
(Bernadette:)What did you tell your boss?
(Amy:)Oh, I was very clever, I did it in stages.
At 7 last night I called
about a problem at the lab...
(Amy:)...and casually mentioned
I was going out for seafood.
At 9:30, I called and told him
that one of my scallops tasted weird.
At 11:30, I called and said
I was throwing up like a fire hose.
At 12:45, I called and made nothing
but dry-heaving sounds.
And now I'm going to Disneyland!
(Bernadette:)Penny, what did you say?
(Penny:)I work at the Cheesecake Factory.
I said, "Bye."
(Amy:)So, what are we gonna do first?
I don't know about you, but I'm going to the
place that gives you a princess makeover.